

MD Maruf Islam Web Developer

DE PHONE: +8801759887993

EMAIL: maruf4426@diu.edu.bd

■ WEBSITE : https://islammaruf.github.io/



PROFILE

I'm a Web Developer - having understanding of Object-Oriented Programming and Database Design, have hands-on experience working with PHP, Javascript, Laravel, jQuery, REST API. Currently, I am working at Colgis BD LTD. I like to work with my team and love to share and gather knowledge. Besides, I am learning and having knowledge of Javascript framework such as Vue js, React js, Express js.



EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer | Skylark Soft Limited

FEB 2019 - DEC 2019

Experience in garments related ERP system

- Work on order, purchase order and generate report like order confirmation list, order recap summery report depends on dates.
- Work on user to user chat system with pusher, ¡Query and notification system using laravel notification via database.
- Work on different portion of inventory system like purchase requisition, purchase receive.
- Work on ERP dashboard and create dashboard according to user requirement
- Work experience on different portion like leads, contact, accounts, opportunities in CRM. URL: http://172.104.171.248:69/
- Work on SaaS based software and handle payment system with third party API like Fast Spring . URL : www.offcutter.com

Software Programmer | Colgis BD Ltd

JAN 2020 - Present

- Work on warehouse management system.
- Work on user management sytem



EDUCATION

BSC in CSE | Daffodil International University

SEP 2014 - DEC 2018

CGPA 3.20 OUT OF 4.0

EX SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, ES6, jQuery, Ajax, Vue js, React js
- Knowledge of Design Pattern
- Knowledge of Laravel core like dependency injection, Reflection api, service container, some idea about request life cycle
- Database Management System
- Knowledge of Object Oriented Programing
- Version Controlling System such as Git
- Basic idea on CI like Travis CI